[
  {
    "question": "Who won the French Open (Men's Singles) in 1968?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Rod Laver",
      "yellow": "Manuel Santana",
      "blue": "Ken Rosewall",
      "green": "Ilie Năstase"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the French Open (Men's Singles) in 1974?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Björn Borg",
      "yellow": "Jimmy Connors",
      "blue": "Guillermo Vilas",
      "green": "Ilie Năstase"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the French Open (Men's Singles) in 1983?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Ivan Lendl",
      "yellow": "John McEnroe",
      "blue": "Guillermo Vilas",
      "green": "Mats Wilander"
    },
    "correct": "green"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the French Open (Men's Singles) in 1990?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Andre Agassi",
      "yellow": "Stefan Edberg",
      "blue": "Ivan Lendl",
      "green": "Andrés Gómez"
    },
    "correct": "green"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the French Open (Men's Singles) in 2000?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Andre Agassi",
      "yellow": "Carlos Moyá",
      "blue": "Gustavo Kuerten",
      "green": "Marat Safin"
    },
    "correct": "blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the French Open (Men's Singles) in 2005?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Roger Federer",
      "yellow": "Gastón Gaudio",
      "blue": "Rafael Nadal",
      "green": "Juan Carlos Ferrero"
    },
    "correct": "blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the French Open (Men's Singles) in 2008?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Rafael Nadal",
      "yellow": "Andy Murray",
      "blue": "Roger Federer",
      "green": "Novak Djokovic"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the French Open (Men's Singles) in 2015?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Stan Wawrinka",
      "yellow": "Andy Murray",
      "blue": "Novak Djokovic",
      "green": "Rafael Nadal"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the French Open (Men's Singles) in 2020?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Rafael Nadal",
      "yellow": "Alexander Zverev",
      "blue": "Novak Djokovic",
      "green": "Dominic Thiem"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the French Open (Men's Singles) in 2023?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Novak Djokovic",
      "yellow": "Casper Ruud",
      "blue": "Carlos Alcaraz",
      "green": "Rafael Nadal"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  }
]